{"id": "sample_00000", "tokens": ["Goldman", "Sachs", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Mumbai,", "said", "Maria", "Garcia."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00001", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Singapore", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Amazon."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00002", "tokens": ["According", "to", "NASA,", "Anna", "Martinez", "will", "relocate", "to", "Tokyo."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00003", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Dubai", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Amazon."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00004", "tokens": ["Lisa", "Anderson", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Tokyo", "joined", "World", "Health", "Organization", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00005", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Microsoft,", "Robert", "Brown", "will", "relocate", "to", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00006", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Goldman", "Sachs,", "John", "Smith", "will", "relocate", "to", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00007", "tokens": ["Amazon", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Dubai,", "said", "Anna", "Martinez."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00008", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Toronto", "joined", "Microsoft", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00009", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "traveled", "from", "London", "to", "meet", "with", "NASA", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00010", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "visited", "Toronto", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00011", "tokens": ["John", "Smith", "traveled", "from", "London", "to", "meet", "with", "Goldman", "Sachs", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00012", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "visited", "Tokyo", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00013", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "and", "colleagues", "from", "London", "joined", "NASA", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00014", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Tesla", "in", "Mumbai", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00015", "tokens": ["John", "Smith,", "CEO", "of", "Tesla,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Toronto."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00016", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Goldman", "Sachs,", "David", "Chen", "will", "relocate", "to", "Tokyo."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00017", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown,", "CEO", "of", "Harvard", "University,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00018", "tokens": ["Lisa", "Anderson", "visited", "Paris", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00019", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee,", "CEO", "of", "BBC,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00020", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Toronto", "joined", "FIFA", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00021", "tokens": ["According", "to", "BBC,", "Michael", "Lee", "will", "relocate", "to", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00022", "tokens": ["John", "Smith,", "CEO", "of", "Microsoft,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00023", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "FIFA", "in", "London", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00024", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "and", "colleagues", "from", "New", "York", "joined", "Goldman", "Sachs", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00025", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "traveled", "from", "Dubai", "to", "meet", "with", "BBC", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00026", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "traveled", "from", "Tokyo", "to", "meet", "with", "United", "Nations", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00027", "tokens": ["Goldman", "Sachs", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Lisa", "Anderson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00028", "tokens": ["BBC", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Emily", "Williams."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00029", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Goldman", "Sachs,", "Sarah", "Johnson", "will", "relocate", "to", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00030", "tokens": ["According", "to", "World", "Health", "Organization,", "Lisa", "Anderson", "will", "relocate", "to", "Mumbai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00031", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "visited", "London", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00032", "tokens": ["John", "Smith,", "CEO", "of", "Harvard", "University,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Singapore."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00033", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan,", "CEO", "of", "United", "Nations,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00034", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan,", "CEO", "of", "United", "Nations,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00035", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Emily", "Williams."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00036", "tokens": ["FIFA", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Michael", "Lee."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00037", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams", "visited", "Dubai", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00038", "tokens": ["Lisa", "Anderson", "visited", "New", "York", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00039", "tokens": ["Lisa", "Anderson,", "CEO", "of", "Goldman", "Sachs,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Singapore."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00040", "tokens": ["According", "to", "FIFA,", "Ahmed", "Hassan", "will", "relocate", "to", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00041", "tokens": ["The", "Tokyo", "office", "of", "BBC", "welcomed", "Emily", "Williams", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00042", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Maria", "Garcia."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00043", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "visited", "Singapore", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00044", "tokens": ["John", "Smith", "traveled", "from", "New", "York", "to", "meet", "with", "Harvard", "University", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00045", "tokens": ["NASA", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Anna", "Martinez."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00046", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "FIFA", "in", "Dubai", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00047", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "New", "York", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Tesla."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00048", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "visited", "Singapore", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00049", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "BBC", "in", "Dubai", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00050", "tokens": ["According", "to", "World", "Health", "Organization,", "Ahmed", "Hassan", "will", "relocate", "to", "Mumbai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00051", "tokens": ["NASA", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Michael", "Lee."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00052", "tokens": ["The", "Paris", "office", "of", "Amazon", "welcomed", "Michael", "Lee", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00053", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Berlin", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Amazon."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00054", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia,", "CEO", "of", "NASA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00055", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "visited", "Tokyo", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00056", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "FIFA", "in", "Singapore", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00057", "tokens": ["Harvard", "University", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Emily", "Williams."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00058", "tokens": ["BBC", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "David", "Chen."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00059", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "London", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "BBC."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00060", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "traveled", "from", "Toronto", "to", "meet", "with", "Goldman", "Sachs", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00061", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan,", "CEO", "of", "NASA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00062", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Amazon", "in", "London", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00063", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "NASA", "in", "London", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00064", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Mumbai", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "United", "Nations."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00065", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Tesla,", "Robert", "Brown", "will", "relocate", "to", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00066", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Tokyo,", "said", "Anna", "Martinez."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00067", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez,", "CEO", "of", "FIFA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Tokyo."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00068", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown,", "CEO", "of", "United", "Nations,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Singapore."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00069", "tokens": ["According", "to", "FIFA,", "John", "Smith", "will", "relocate", "to", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00070", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Anna", "Martinez."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00071", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Paris,", "said", "Michael", "Lee."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00072", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "visited", "Singapore", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00073", "tokens": ["The", "Dubai", "office", "of", "NASA", "welcomed", "Emily", "Williams", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00074", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "BBC", "in", "Toronto", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00075", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan,", "CEO", "of", "BBC,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Singapore."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00076", "tokens": ["The", "New", "York", "office", "of", "Tesla", "welcomed", "Michael", "Lee", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00077", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Mumbai", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "NASA."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00078", "tokens": ["According", "to", "NASA,", "Ahmed", "Hassan", "will", "relocate", "to", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00079", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "United", "Nations", "in", "Toronto", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00080", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Sarah", "Johnson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00081", "tokens": ["The", "London", "office", "of", "Goldman", "Sachs", "welcomed", "Anna", "Martinez", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00082", "tokens": ["According", "to", "United", "Nations,", "Sarah", "Johnson", "will", "relocate", "to", "Dubai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00083", "tokens": ["Amazon", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Emily", "Williams."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00084", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "visited", "Toronto", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00085", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Maria", "Garcia."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00086", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan,", "CEO", "of", "BBC,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00087", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "visited", "London", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00088", "tokens": ["BBC", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Sarah", "Johnson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00089", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "visited", "Tokyo", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00090", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "New", "York", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Goldman", "Sachs."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00091", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Mumbai", "joined", "World", "Health", "Organization", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00092", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson,", "CEO", "of", "FIFA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00093", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Goldman", "Sachs,", "Anna", "Martinez", "will", "relocate", "to", "Dubai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00094", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "FIFA", "in", "Toronto", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00095", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia,", "CEO", "of", "Harvard", "University,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00096", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Ahmed", "Hassan."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00097", "tokens": ["BBC", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Sydney,", "said", "Robert", "Brown."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00098", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams,", "CEO", "of", "Microsoft,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Tokyo."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00099", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Tesla,", "Robert", "Brown", "will", "relocate", "to", "Tokyo."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00100", "tokens": ["John", "Smith,", "CEO", "of", "World", "Health", "Organization,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Mumbai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00101", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "New", "York", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "NASA."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00102", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "World", "Health", "Organization", "in", "Singapore", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00103", "tokens": ["Lisa", "Anderson,", "CEO", "of", "NASA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00104", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "traveled", "from", "Singapore", "to", "meet", "with", "FIFA", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00105", "tokens": ["Tesla", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Tokyo,", "said", "Robert", "Brown."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00106", "tokens": ["According", "to", "NASA,", "Emily", "Williams", "will", "relocate", "to", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00107", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "United", "Nations", "in", "Berlin", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00108", "tokens": ["Goldman", "Sachs", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Dubai,", "said", "Lisa", "Anderson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00109", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Paris", "joined", "Amazon", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00110", "tokens": ["John", "Smith", "visited", "New", "York", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00111", "tokens": ["The", "Singapore", "office", "of", "Microsoft", "welcomed", "Ahmed", "Hassan", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00112", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "London", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "FIFA."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00113", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams,", "CEO", "of", "United", "Nations,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00114", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "visited", "Paris", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00115", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Sydney", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Harvard", "University."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00116", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Berlin", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Microsoft."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00117", "tokens": ["According", "to", "United", "Nations,", "Robert", "Brown", "will", "relocate", "to", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00118", "tokens": ["According", "to", "World", "Health", "Organization,", "Lisa", "Anderson", "will", "relocate", "to", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00119", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown,", "CEO", "of", "United", "Nations,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Toronto."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00120", "tokens": ["BBC", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Maria", "Garcia."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00121", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "visited", "London", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00122", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "visited", "New", "York", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00123", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "visited", "Singapore", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00124", "tokens": ["Harvard", "University", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Berlin,", "said", "Lisa", "Anderson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00125", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams", "traveled", "from", "Singapore", "to", "meet", "with", "World", "Health", "Organization", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00126", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Michael", "Lee."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00127", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Singapore,", "said", "Lisa", "Anderson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00128", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Toronto", "joined", "United", "Nations", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00129", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "visited", "London", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00130", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "United", "Nations", "in", "Berlin", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00131", "tokens": ["The", "Berlin", "office", "of", "Goldman", "Sachs", "welcomed", "Michael", "Lee", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00132", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "visited", "Paris", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00133", "tokens": ["According", "to", "World", "Health", "Organization,", "Anna", "Martinez", "will", "relocate", "to", "London."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00134", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "London", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "BBC."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00135", "tokens": ["The", "Tokyo", "office", "of", "World", "Health", "Organization", "welcomed", "Sarah", "Johnson", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00136", "tokens": ["According", "to", "FIFA,", "Ahmed", "Hassan", "will", "relocate", "to", "Tokyo."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00137", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Goldman", "Sachs", "in", "Dubai", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00138", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "traveled", "from", "Mumbai", "to", "meet", "with", "United", "Nations", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00139", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez", "and", "colleagues", "from", "New", "York", "joined", "FIFA", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00140", "tokens": ["According", "to", "United", "Nations,", "Robert", "Brown", "will", "relocate", "to", "Toronto."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00141", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Berlin", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "World", "Health", "Organization."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00142", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "and", "colleagues", "from", "New", "York", "joined", "BBC", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00143", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams", "visited", "Tokyo", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00144", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Mumbai", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Amazon."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00145", "tokens": ["Harvard", "University", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "London,", "said", "Emily", "Williams."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00146", "tokens": ["According", "to", "World", "Health", "Organization,", "Robert", "Brown", "will", "relocate", "to", "Singapore."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00147", "tokens": ["The", "Toronto", "office", "of", "Microsoft", "welcomed", "Sarah", "Johnson", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00148", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "NASA", "in", "London", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00149", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia,", "CEO", "of", "Harvard", "University,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00150", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown,", "CEO", "of", "FIFA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00151", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "London", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Amazon."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00152", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "visited", "Tokyo", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00153", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Berlin,", "said", "Lisa", "Anderson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00154", "tokens": ["Lisa", "Anderson", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Singapore", "joined", "FIFA", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00155", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Singapore", "joined", "United", "Nations", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00156", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Dubai", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "FIFA."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00157", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "London", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "BBC."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00158", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "traveled", "from", "Dubai", "to", "meet", "with", "BBC", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00159", "tokens": ["The", "New", "York", "office", "of", "Harvard", "University", "welcomed", "Anna", "Martinez", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00160", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "visited", "Sydney", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00161", "tokens": ["Lisa", "Anderson,", "CEO", "of", "Microsoft,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Dubai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00162", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "BBC", "in", "Dubai", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00163", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Toronto,", "said", "Lisa", "Anderson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00164", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Lisa", "Anderson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00165", "tokens": ["Harvard", "University", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Ahmed", "Hassan."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00166", "tokens": ["Lisa", "Anderson", "visited", "London", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00167", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Tesla,", "Emily", "Williams", "will", "relocate", "to", "Mumbai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00168", "tokens": ["The", "Singapore", "office", "of", "Tesla", "welcomed", "Michael", "Lee", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00169", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "traveled", "from", "Berlin", "to", "meet", "with", "BBC", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00170", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams,", "CEO", "of", "NASA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00171", "tokens": ["John", "Smith", "traveled", "from", "Dubai", "to", "meet", "with", "Tesla", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00172", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez,", "CEO", "of", "United", "Nations,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00173", "tokens": ["John", "Smith", "traveled", "from", "New", "York", "to", "meet", "with", "World", "Health", "Organization", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00174", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown,", "CEO", "of", "BBC,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Dubai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00175", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Microsoft", "in", "Berlin", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00176", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "visited", "Toronto", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00177", "tokens": ["Amazon", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Anna", "Martinez."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00178", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Berlin", "joined", "FIFA", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00179", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "BBC", "in", "Sydney", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00180", "tokens": ["The", "Paris", "office", "of", "Amazon", "welcomed", "Sarah", "Johnson", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00181", "tokens": ["NASA", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Maria", "Garcia."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00182", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Dubai", "joined", "World", "Health", "Organization", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00183", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "NASA", "in", "Dubai", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00184", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Sydney", "joined", "Harvard", "University", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00185", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "traveled", "from", "New", "York", "to", "meet", "with", "United", "Nations", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00186", "tokens": ["Harvard", "University", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Mumbai,", "said", "Sarah", "Johnson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00187", "tokens": ["The", "New", "York", "office", "of", "NASA", "welcomed", "David", "Chen", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00188", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Toronto", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Amazon."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00189", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Harvard", "University", "in", "Berlin", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00190", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Microsoft", "in", "Dubai", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00191", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Singapore", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Tesla."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00192", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "visited", "Paris", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00193", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams,", "CEO", "of", "BBC,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00194", "tokens": ["Goldman", "Sachs", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Singapore,", "said", "David", "Chen."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00195", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan,", "CEO", "of", "World", "Health", "Organization,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Tokyo."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00196", "tokens": ["According", "to", "United", "Nations,", "Emily", "Williams", "will", "relocate", "to", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00197", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Berlin", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "FIFA."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00198", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Dubai", "joined", "United", "Nations", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00199", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Paris", "joined", "BBC", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00200", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "and", "colleagues", "from", "London", "joined", "Microsoft", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00201", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown,", "CEO", "of", "Microsoft,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00202", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia,", "CEO", "of", "World", "Health", "Organization,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00203", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "London,", "said", "Ahmed", "Hassan."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00204", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "United", "Nations", "in", "Singapore", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00205", "tokens": ["NASA", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Berlin,", "said", "Michael", "Lee."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00206", "tokens": ["According", "to", "NASA,", "Emily", "Williams", "will", "relocate", "to", "London."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00207", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Singapore", "joined", "World", "Health", "Organization", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00208", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Toronto,", "said", "Emily", "Williams."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00209", "tokens": ["NASA", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "New", "York,", "said", "Lisa", "Anderson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00210", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Harvard", "University", "in", "Dubai", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00211", "tokens": ["The", "Paris", "office", "of", "Microsoft", "welcomed", "John", "Smith", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00212", "tokens": ["Amazon", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Berlin,", "said", "Ahmed", "Hassan."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00213", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez", "visited", "Toronto", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00214", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "visited", "Sydney", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00215", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "traveled", "from", "Mumbai", "to", "meet", "with", "Tesla", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00216", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Paris", "joined", "Tesla", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00217", "tokens": ["According", "to", "FIFA,", "Robert", "Brown", "will", "relocate", "to", "Singapore."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00218", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez,", "CEO", "of", "Goldman", "Sachs,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00219", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Tesla,", "Emily", "Williams", "will", "relocate", "to", "Tokyo."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00220", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "World", "Health", "Organization", "in", "Sydney", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00221", "tokens": ["The", "Dubai", "office", "of", "NASA", "welcomed", "Emily", "Williams", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00222", "tokens": ["FIFA", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Singapore,", "said", "Ahmed", "Hassan."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00223", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Amazon,", "Sarah", "Johnson", "will", "relocate", "to", "Mumbai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00224", "tokens": ["The", "Singapore", "office", "of", "Harvard", "University", "welcomed", "Sarah", "Johnson", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00225", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Toronto", "joined", "NASA", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00226", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Dubai", "joined", "Harvard", "University", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00227", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Amazon", "in", "Tokyo", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00228", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Toronto", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "NASA."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00229", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan,", "CEO", "of", "Microsoft,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "London."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00230", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "traveled", "from", "Mumbai", "to", "meet", "with", "Goldman", "Sachs", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00231", "tokens": ["According", "to", "NASA,", "David", "Chen", "will", "relocate", "to", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00232", "tokens": ["John", "Smith,", "CEO", "of", "United", "Nations,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00233", "tokens": ["The", "Dubai", "office", "of", "NASA", "welcomed", "Ahmed", "Hassan", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00234", "tokens": ["The", "Sydney", "office", "of", "BBC", "welcomed", "Sarah", "Johnson", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00235", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "and", "colleagues", "from", "London", "joined", "NASA", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00236", "tokens": ["Amazon", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Paris,", "said", "John", "Smith."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00237", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez", "traveled", "from", "Toronto", "to", "meet", "with", "FIFA", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00238", "tokens": ["The", "Sydney", "office", "of", "BBC", "welcomed", "Emily", "Williams", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00239", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee,", "CEO", "of", "World", "Health", "Organization,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00240", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Robert", "Brown."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00241", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "visited", "Berlin", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00242", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Amazon,", "Ahmed", "Hassan", "will", "relocate", "to", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00243", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "traveled", "from", "London", "to", "meet", "with", "FIFA", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00244", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "traveled", "from", "Singapore", "to", "meet", "with", "Tesla", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00245", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "visited", "London", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00246", "tokens": ["Goldman", "Sachs", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Ahmed", "Hassan."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00247", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Toronto", "joined", "World", "Health", "Organization", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00248", "tokens": ["The", "Toronto", "office", "of", "Amazon", "welcomed", "Maria", "Garcia", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00249", "tokens": ["John", "Smith", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Toronto", "joined", "Microsoft", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00250", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "FIFA", "in", "London", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00251", "tokens": ["Tesla", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Tokyo,", "said", "John", "Smith."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00252", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Dubai", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "NASA."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00253", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown,", "CEO", "of", "FIFA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Mumbai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00254", "tokens": ["The", "Sydney", "office", "of", "Goldman", "Sachs", "welcomed", "Emily", "Williams", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00255", "tokens": ["Lisa", "Anderson", "and", "colleagues", "from", "London", "joined", "Microsoft", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00256", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "traveled", "from", "Toronto", "to", "meet", "with", "Tesla", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00257", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Singapore", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Microsoft."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00258", "tokens": ["According", "to", "United", "Nations,", "David", "Chen", "will", "relocate", "to", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00259", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Berlin", "joined", "Tesla", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00260", "tokens": ["According", "to", "NASA,", "Emily", "Williams", "will", "relocate", "to", "Toronto."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00261", "tokens": ["According", "to", "FIFA,", "Robert", "Brown", "will", "relocate", "to", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00262", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Michael", "Lee."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00263", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "visited", "Sydney", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00264", "tokens": ["According", "to", "BBC,", "Lisa", "Anderson", "will", "relocate", "to", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00265", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Harvard", "University", "in", "Paris", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00266", "tokens": ["According", "to", "FIFA,", "Michael", "Lee", "will", "relocate", "to", "London."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00267", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Paris", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Amazon."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00268", "tokens": ["The", "Sydney", "office", "of", "World", "Health", "Organization", "welcomed", "Sarah", "Johnson", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00269", "tokens": ["John", "Smith", "visited", "Sydney", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00270", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams,", "CEO", "of", "NASA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Tokyo."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00271", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "traveled", "from", "Dubai", "to", "meet", "with", "Amazon", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00272", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams", "and", "colleagues", "from", "New", "York", "joined", "Tesla", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00273", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Berlin", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "NASA."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00274", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Tesla", "in", "Mumbai", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00275", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez", "visited", "New", "York", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00276", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee,", "CEO", "of", "FIFA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Toronto."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00277", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Harvard", "University,", "Sarah", "Johnson", "will", "relocate", "to", "Tokyo."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00278", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams,", "CEO", "of", "World", "Health", "Organization,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Dubai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00279", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "London", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Microsoft."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00280", "tokens": ["Harvard", "University", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Singapore,", "said", "John", "Smith."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00281", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "traveled", "from", "Singapore", "to", "meet", "with", "NASA", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00282", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "visited", "Berlin", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00283", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "traveled", "from", "Tokyo", "to", "meet", "with", "United", "Nations", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00284", "tokens": ["John", "Smith,", "CEO", "of", "Tesla,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Mumbai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00285", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Ahmed", "Hassan."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00286", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Microsoft", "in", "London", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00287", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "FIFA", "in", "Tokyo", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00288", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Amazon,", "Michael", "Lee", "will", "relocate", "to", "Toronto."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00289", "tokens": ["John", "Smith", "visited", "Mumbai", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00290", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Dubai", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Microsoft."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00291", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Amazon,", "Robert", "Brown", "will", "relocate", "to", "Dubai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00292", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Amazon", "in", "Dubai", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00293", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Singapore", "joined", "Microsoft", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00294", "tokens": ["John", "Smith", "traveled", "from", "Singapore", "to", "meet", "with", "World", "Health", "Organization", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00295", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "United", "Nations", "in", "Tokyo", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00296", "tokens": ["BBC", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Sarah", "Johnson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00297", "tokens": ["Goldman", "Sachs", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "David", "Chen."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00298", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Amazon,", "David", "Chen", "will", "relocate", "to", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00299", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Berlin,", "said", "Ahmed", "Hassan."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00300", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "visited", "London", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00301", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Emily", "Williams."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00302", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "traveled", "from", "Paris", "to", "meet", "with", "United", "Nations", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00303", "tokens": ["Goldman", "Sachs", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Sydney,", "said", "David", "Chen."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00304", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Maria", "Garcia."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00305", "tokens": ["According", "to", "FIFA,", "Anna", "Martinez", "will", "relocate", "to", "Dubai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00306", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "United", "Nations", "in", "Dubai", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00307", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Singapore", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Harvard", "University."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00308", "tokens": ["FIFA", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Robert", "Brown."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00309", "tokens": ["The", "Dubai", "office", "of", "Amazon", "welcomed", "Anna", "Martinez", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00310", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "traveled", "from", "Singapore", "to", "meet", "with", "Microsoft", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00311", "tokens": ["David", "Chen,", "CEO", "of", "Goldman", "Sachs,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00312", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Dubai", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "FIFA."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00313", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Tokyo,", "said", "Anna", "Martinez."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00314", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Harvard", "University", "in", "Berlin", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00315", "tokens": ["Lisa", "Anderson,", "CEO", "of", "Tesla,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Toronto."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00316", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Mumbai", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "World", "Health", "Organization."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00317", "tokens": ["BBC", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Sarah", "Johnson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00318", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "World", "Health", "Organization", "in", "New", "York", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00319", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams,", "CEO", "of", "NASA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Tokyo."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00320", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia,", "CEO", "of", "FIFA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00321", "tokens": ["Amazon", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "London,", "said", "Robert", "Brown."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00322", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "visited", "Sydney", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00323", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown,", "CEO", "of", "BBC,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00324", "tokens": ["The", "Singapore", "office", "of", "United", "Nations", "welcomed", "Lisa", "Anderson", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00325", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "traveled", "from", "Toronto", "to", "meet", "with", "World", "Health", "Organization", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00326", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Tesla,", "Lisa", "Anderson", "will", "relocate", "to", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00327", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Paris", "joined", "Goldman", "Sachs", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00328", "tokens": ["The", "New", "York", "office", "of", "Amazon", "welcomed", "David", "Chen", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00329", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "traveled", "from", "Berlin", "to", "meet", "with", "Amazon", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00330", "tokens": ["According", "to", "World", "Health", "Organization,", "John", "Smith", "will", "relocate", "to", "Dubai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00331", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "traveled", "from", "Tokyo", "to", "meet", "with", "BBC", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00332", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Robert", "Brown."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00333", "tokens": ["BBC", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Sarah", "Johnson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00334", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "traveled", "from", "Paris", "to", "meet", "with", "Amazon", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00335", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "visited", "Berlin", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00336", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams", "visited", "Berlin", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00337", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "visited", "Dubai", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00338", "tokens": ["BBC", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Tokyo,", "said", "Sarah", "Johnson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00339", "tokens": ["David", "Chen,", "CEO", "of", "Microsoft,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Singapore."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00340", "tokens": ["Goldman", "Sachs", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Singapore,", "said", "Emily", "Williams."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00341", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Amazon", "in", "London", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00342", "tokens": ["The", "Toronto", "office", "of", "NASA", "welcomed", "Maria", "Garcia", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00343", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez,", "CEO", "of", "Goldman", "Sachs,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00344", "tokens": ["BBC", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Lisa", "Anderson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00345", "tokens": ["David", "Chen,", "CEO", "of", "World", "Health", "Organization,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Dubai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00346", "tokens": ["The", "Tokyo", "office", "of", "BBC", "welcomed", "Lisa", "Anderson", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00347", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams", "traveled", "from", "Sydney", "to", "meet", "with", "Tesla", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00348", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Berlin", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Goldman", "Sachs."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00349", "tokens": ["The", "Dubai", "office", "of", "Tesla", "welcomed", "David", "Chen", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00350", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "traveled", "from", "Singapore", "to", "meet", "with", "Microsoft", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00351", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Sydney,", "said", "Sarah", "Johnson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00352", "tokens": ["John", "Smith", "traveled", "from", "Singapore", "to", "meet", "with", "BBC", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00353", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez", "traveled", "from", "Paris", "to", "meet", "with", "Tesla", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00354", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Sydney", "joined", "Goldman", "Sachs", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00355", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Berlin", "joined", "Harvard", "University", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00356", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams", "visited", "Paris", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00357", "tokens": ["According", "to", "BBC,", "John", "Smith", "will", "relocate", "to", "Singapore."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00358", "tokens": ["Tesla", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Dubai,", "said", "Sarah", "Johnson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00359", "tokens": ["FIFA", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Dubai,", "said", "Sarah", "Johnson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00360", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams,", "CEO", "of", "Goldman", "Sachs,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00361", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Microsoft", "in", "New", "York", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00362", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson,", "CEO", "of", "Microsoft,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00363", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Paris", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Amazon."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00364", "tokens": ["According", "to", "FIFA,", "Anna", "Martinez", "will", "relocate", "to", "Mumbai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00365", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "United", "Nations", "in", "Toronto", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00366", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Berlin", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Tesla."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00367", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "visited", "Sydney", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00368", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson,", "CEO", "of", "Tesla,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00369", "tokens": ["Amazon", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Ahmed", "Hassan."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00370", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Amazon", "in", "London", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00371", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "NASA", "in", "Singapore", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00372", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan,", "CEO", "of", "Harvard", "University,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00373", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Tokyo", "joined", "United", "Nations", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00374", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "visited", "Paris", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00375", "tokens": ["The", "Berlin", "office", "of", "Goldman", "Sachs", "welcomed", "Maria", "Garcia", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00376", "tokens": ["According", "to", "BBC,", "Michael", "Lee", "will", "relocate", "to", "Toronto."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00377", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Berlin", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "World", "Health", "Organization."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00378", "tokens": ["The", "Singapore", "office", "of", "NASA", "welcomed", "Robert", "Brown", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00379", "tokens": ["According", "to", "BBC,", "Lisa", "Anderson", "will", "relocate", "to", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00380", "tokens": ["The", "Mumbai", "office", "of", "Amazon", "welcomed", "David", "Chen", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00381", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Dubai", "joined", "Microsoft", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00382", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "visited", "Paris", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00383", "tokens": ["The", "Dubai", "office", "of", "NASA", "welcomed", "Ahmed", "Hassan", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00384", "tokens": ["Lisa", "Anderson,", "CEO", "of", "United", "Nations,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Singapore."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00385", "tokens": ["According", "to", "FIFA,", "John", "Smith", "will", "relocate", "to", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00386", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "visited", "London", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00387", "tokens": ["The", "Singapore", "office", "of", "World", "Health", "Organization", "welcomed", "Lisa", "Anderson", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00388", "tokens": ["According", "to", "World", "Health", "Organization,", "Ahmed", "Hassan", "will", "relocate", "to", "Mumbai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00389", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez", "and", "colleagues", "from", "London", "joined", "Tesla", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00390", "tokens": ["The", "Toronto", "office", "of", "Goldman", "Sachs", "welcomed", "David", "Chen", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00391", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Mumbai", "joined", "United", "Nations", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00392", "tokens": ["According", "to", "BBC,", "John", "Smith", "will", "relocate", "to", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00393", "tokens": ["John", "Smith", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Berlin", "joined", "Goldman", "Sachs", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00394", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "FIFA", "in", "Berlin", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00395", "tokens": ["Amazon", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Emily", "Williams."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00396", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "and", "colleagues", "from", "New", "York", "joined", "Tesla", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00397", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Toronto", "joined", "NASA", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00398", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Tokyo", "joined", "BBC", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00399", "tokens": ["Goldman", "Sachs", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Sydney,", "said", "Anna", "Martinez."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00400", "tokens": ["David", "Chen,", "CEO", "of", "Harvard", "University,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Dubai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00401", "tokens": ["Tesla", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "London,", "said", "Robert", "Brown."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00402", "tokens": ["The", "Paris", "office", "of", "World", "Health", "Organization", "welcomed", "Maria", "Garcia", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00403", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown,", "CEO", "of", "FIFA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00404", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Amazon", "in", "Berlin", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00405", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia,", "CEO", "of", "Tesla,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Mumbai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00406", "tokens": ["The", "Toronto", "office", "of", "World", "Health", "Organization", "welcomed", "John", "Smith", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00407", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams", "traveled", "from", "Singapore", "to", "meet", "with", "Tesla", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00408", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "United", "Nations", "in", "London", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00409", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "World", "Health", "Organization", "in", "Tokyo", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00410", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "visited", "Dubai", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00411", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia,", "CEO", "of", "NASA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "London."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00412", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Sydney", "joined", "World", "Health", "Organization", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00413", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Harvard", "University", "in", "Sydney", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00414", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Singapore", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "FIFA."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00415", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Emily", "Williams."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00416", "tokens": ["According", "to", "United", "Nations,", "Ahmed", "Hassan", "will", "relocate", "to", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00417", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee,", "CEO", "of", "Microsoft,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00418", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "World", "Health", "Organization", "in", "Paris", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00419", "tokens": ["According", "to", "FIFA,", "Michael", "Lee", "will", "relocate", "to", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00420", "tokens": ["According", "to", "NASA,", "David", "Chen", "will", "relocate", "to", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00421", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Tokyo", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "NASA."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00422", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "visited", "London", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00423", "tokens": ["Amazon", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Sarah", "Johnson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00424", "tokens": ["According", "to", "FIFA,", "Michael", "Lee", "will", "relocate", "to", "Mumbai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00425", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Berlin", "joined", "Microsoft", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00426", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "traveled", "from", "Berlin", "to", "meet", "with", "Amazon", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00427", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams", "traveled", "from", "New", "York", "to", "meet", "with", "Goldman", "Sachs", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00428", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Amazon,", "Sarah", "Johnson", "will", "relocate", "to", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00429", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Tesla,", "Maria", "Garcia", "will", "relocate", "to", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00430", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "BBC", "in", "Singapore", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00431", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Sydney", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Harvard", "University."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00432", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "traveled", "from", "Mumbai", "to", "meet", "with", "Harvard", "University", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00433", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Mumbai", "joined", "World", "Health", "Organization", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00434", "tokens": ["Lisa", "Anderson", "traveled", "from", "Singapore", "to", "meet", "with", "Goldman", "Sachs", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00435", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "traveled", "from", "Paris", "to", "meet", "with", "Amazon", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00436", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "visited", "Toronto", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00437", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Toronto", "joined", "Microsoft", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00438", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Mumbai", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Microsoft."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00439", "tokens": ["Lisa", "Anderson", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Tokyo", "joined", "FIFA", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00440", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson,", "CEO", "of", "United", "Nations,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Singapore."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00441", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Harvard", "University", "in", "London", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00442", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan,", "CEO", "of", "Harvard", "University,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Berlin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00443", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "and", "colleagues", "from", "New", "York", "joined", "Microsoft", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00444", "tokens": ["Harvard", "University", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Singapore,", "said", "David", "Chen."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00445", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams", "traveled", "from", "Singapore", "to", "meet", "with", "United", "Nations", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00446", "tokens": ["John", "Smith,", "CEO", "of", "Goldman", "Sachs,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Toronto."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00447", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "visited", "New", "York", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00448", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia,", "CEO", "of", "FIFA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "London."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00449", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "and", "colleagues", "from", "London", "joined", "World", "Health", "Organization", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00450", "tokens": ["The", "Sydney", "office", "of", "FIFA", "welcomed", "Maria", "Garcia", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00451", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "traveled", "from", "Mumbai", "to", "meet", "with", "BBC", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00452", "tokens": ["Anna", "Martinez", "visited", "New", "York", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00453", "tokens": ["David", "Chen", "visited", "Paris", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00454", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee,", "CEO", "of", "NASA,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00455", "tokens": ["FIFA", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Tokyo,", "said", "John", "Smith."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00456", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "visited", "Tokyo", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00457", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "traveled", "from", "Tokyo", "to", "meet", "with", "World", "Health", "Organization", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00458", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Dubai", "joined", "FIFA", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00459", "tokens": ["FIFA", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Sydney,", "said", "Michael", "Lee."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00460", "tokens": ["The", "Toronto", "office", "of", "FIFA", "welcomed", "Sarah", "Johnson", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00461", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Toronto", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "FIFA."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00462", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "visited", "Mumbai", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00463", "tokens": ["Harvard", "University", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Mumbai,", "said", "Maria", "Garcia."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00464", "tokens": ["Goldman", "Sachs", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Maria", "Garcia."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00465", "tokens": ["Lisa", "Anderson", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Berlin", "joined", "Tesla", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00466", "tokens": ["Emily", "Williams", "visited", "Sydney", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00467", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "London,", "said", "Maria", "Garcia."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00468", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Mumbai", "joined", "Goldman", "Sachs", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00469", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Maria", "Garcia."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00470", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Toronto", "joined", "United", "Nations", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00471", "tokens": ["According", "to", "BBC,", "John", "Smith", "will", "relocate", "to", "Paris."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00472", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Harvard", "University,", "John", "Smith", "will", "relocate", "to", "Mumbai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00473", "tokens": ["According", "to", "Harvard", "University,", "Lisa", "Anderson", "will", "relocate", "to", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00474", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Singapore", "joined", "United", "Nations", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00475", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Johnson", "visited", "London", "last", "week", "for", "a", "conference."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00476", "tokens": ["Ahmed", "Hassan", "traveled", "from", "Dubai", "to", "meet", "with", "BBC", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00477", "tokens": ["BBC", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Sydney,", "said", "Robert", "Brown."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00478", "tokens": ["The", "New", "York", "office", "of", "World", "Health", "Organization", "welcomed", "John", "Smith", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00479", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Sydney", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "FIFA."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00480", "tokens": ["Robert", "Brown,", "CEO", "of", "Tesla,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Singapore."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00481", "tokens": ["Amazon", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Ahmed", "Hassan."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00482", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Toronto", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "FIFA."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00483", "tokens": ["John", "Smith,", "CEO", "of", "Goldman", "Sachs,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Sydney."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00484", "tokens": ["FIFA", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Mumbai,", "said", "Lisa", "Anderson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00485", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Paris", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Tesla."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00486", "tokens": ["BBC", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Tokyo,", "said", "Sarah", "Johnson."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00487", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia,", "CEO", "of", "BBC,", "spoke", "at", "the", "event", "in", "Dubai."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00488", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "Tesla", "in", "Paris", "published", "new", "findings."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00489", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Sydney", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "United", "Nations."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00490", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announced", "a", "new", "partnership", "with", "Emily", "Williams."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00491", "tokens": ["According", "to", "World", "Health", "Organization,", "Ahmed", "Hassan", "will", "relocate", "to", "Toronto."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00492", "tokens": ["Amazon", "is", "expanding", "operations", "to", "Toronto,", "said", "Michael", "Lee."], "labels": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00493", "tokens": ["Maria", "Garcia", "and", "colleagues", "from", "Berlin", "joined", "Microsoft", "this", "month."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00494", "tokens": ["The", "meeting", "in", "Singapore", "was", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "Goldman", "Sachs."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00495", "tokens": ["The", "Singapore", "office", "of", "Harvard", "University", "welcomed", "Michael", "Lee", "as", "director."], "labels": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "sample_00496", "tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "traveled", "from", "Paris", "to", "meet", "with", "World", "Health", "Organization", "officials."], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
